<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ResourceList>
  <Resource>
    <Id>1</Id>
    <Tag>Homebuying</Tag>
    <Header>All You Need to Know About Buyer’s Closing Costs</Header>
    <Description>
			Th  home buying experience can be exciting.  You’re ready to settle down or upgrade to more space for your family.
			But with all the action surrounding getting pre-approved, finding a reputable Real Estate Agent and vising open
			houses, there’s one thing that can’t be forgotten during the excitement – your closing costs.
		</Description>
    <ImagePath>/images/Resource/Refinance.jpg</ImagePath>
    <Status>true</Status>
  </Resource>
  <Resource>
    <Id>2</Id>
    <Tag>Homebuying</Tag>
    <Header>Avoid These Common Mistakes When Selling Your Home</Header>
    <Description>
			It’s time consuming, it can be emotional, it’s overwhelming – let’s face it, it’s A LOT when you’re looking to
			put your home on the market.  First time home sellers may find the process frustrating and it’s very common for
			mistakes to be made during the process.  Check out the biggest mistakes to avoid when looking to sell your home.
		</Description>
    <ImagePath>/images/Resource/2.jpg</ImagePath>
    <Status>true</Status>
  </Resource>
  <Resource>
    <Id>3</Id>
    <Tag>Homebuying</Tag>
    <Header>Navigating Today’s Hot Real Estate Market – How To Land A Deal</Header>
    <Description>
			Supply is low which is pushing home prices higher and higher.  In this hot market, it can be hard for buyer’s
			to land a deal.  We break it down to four simple steps below on how to navigate the market and come out on top
			when searching for your next home.
		</Description>
    <ImagePath>/images/Resource/3.jpg</ImagePath>
    <Status>true</Status>
  </Resource>
  <Resource>
    <Id>4</Id>
    <Tag>Homebuying</Tag>
    <Header>Why Should I Get Pre-Approved For A Mortgage?</Header>
    <Description>
			You’re moving across the country – how exciting!  Before you start loading up your moving truck, you want to
			find a place to live.  Just landed your dream job – so many feelings and emotions.  Let’s get the contract
			signed before you start decorating your office.  The same mindset comes into play when you’re looking to
			purchase a new home.  Your first step to ensure everything goes smoothly?  Get pre-approved.  Serious
			homebuyers should start the process by obtaining their pre-approval letter, not by visiting an abundance
			of open houses.
		</Description>
    <ImagePath>/images/Resource/4.jpg</ImagePath>
    <Status>true</Status>
  </Resource>
  <Resource>
    <Id>5</Id>
    <Tag>Homebuying</Tag>
    <Header>Reasons Why You Should Refinance Your Mortgage</Header>
    <Description>
			Unless you’re living under a rock, we’re sure you’ve heard the news that interest rates are at ALL TIME LOWS.
			But what does this mean?  If you are finding it difficult to service your mortgage, or wish to benefit from
			lower interest rates, you can opt for refinancing. Many private and government-controlled home refinancing
			programs are available to the general public. As long as you meet their criteria, you can refinance your
			mortgage.
		</Description>
    <ImagePath>/images/Resource/resource.jpg</ImagePath>
    <Status>true</Status>
  </Resource>
  <Resource>
    <Id>6</Id>
    <Tag>Homebuying</Tag>
    <Header>&lt;b&gt;Sample&lt;/b&gt;</Header>
    <Description>&lt;u&gt;this is sample&lt;/u&gt;</Description>
    <ImagePath>/images/Resource/2.jpg</ImagePath>
    <Status>true</Status>
  </Resource>
  <Resource>
    <Id>7</Id>
    <Tag>Refinancing</Tag>
    <Header>&lt;p&gt;Test For Save Data&lt;/p&gt;</Header>
    <Description>&lt;p&gt;Test For save data of description&lt;/p&gt;</Description>
    <ImagePath>/images/Resource/about-c.png</ImagePath>
    <Status>false</Status>
  </Resource>
  <Resource>
    <Id>8</Id>
    <Tag>Refinancing</Tag>
    <Header>&lt;p&gt;&lt;font color="#0000ff"&gt;This is&lt;/font&gt; &lt;b&gt;Resource Page&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</Header>
    <Description>&lt;p&gt;This is the sample resource page for display under resource section of the application.&lt;/p&gt;</Description>
    <ImagePath>/images/Resource/3.jpg</ImagePath>
    <Status>false</Status>
  </Resource>
  <Resource>
    <Id>9</Id>
    <Tag>Homebuying</Tag>
    <Header>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;Sample Article 4&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</Header>
    <Description>&lt;p&gt;Test or description sample&lt;/p&gt;</Description>
    <ImagePath>/images/Resource/Refinance.jpg</ImagePath>
    <Status>false</Status>
  </Resource>
  <Resource>
    <Id>10</Id>
    <Tag>News &amp; Insight</Tag>
    <Header>&lt;p&gt;test svdf ds&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</Header>
    <Description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;ffdsadfsdfs c ds s&amp;nbsp;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</Description>
    <ImagePath>/images/Resource/2.jpg</ImagePath>
    <Status>false</Status>
  </Resource>
  <Resource>
    <Id>11</Id>
    <Tag>Homebuying</Tag>
    <Header>&lt;p&gt;fsdfdfc cvbcvx&lt;/p&gt;&amp;nbsp;</Header>
    <Description>&lt;p&gt;xcvxdfxcvxcvx&lt;/p&gt;</Description>
    <ImagePath>/images/Resource/2.jpg</ImagePath>
    <Status>false</Status>
  </Resource>
  <Resource>
    <Id>12</Id>
    <Tag>Refinancing</Tag>
    <Header>&lt;p&gt;sample 1 article&lt;/p&gt;</Header>
    <Description>&lt;p&gt;sample description&lt;/p&gt;</Description>
    <ImagePath>/images/Resource/Refinance.jpg</ImagePath>
    <Status>false</Status>
  </Resource>
  <Resource>
    <Id>13</Id>
    <Tag>Homebuying</Tag>
    <Header>&lt;p&gt;Test Hypotec Resource&lt;/p&gt;</Header>
    <Description>&lt;p&gt;Test for &lt;b&gt;add resourec&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</Description>
    <ImagePath>/images/Resource/Jane.jpg</ImagePath>
    <Status>false</Status>
  </Resource>
</ResourceList>